Finding Aid for American Society for Information Science and Technology Records, 1925-2001
University of Michigan Library (Special Collections Research Center)
- AWARDS
  - Individual Awards
    - Award of Merit
      ("Nominee Documentation" folders contain large amounts of correspondence)
      - Jury, 1983-1984 and 1987 (Box 97)
      - Nominations Committee, 1973-1981 (Box 97)
      - Nominees, 1964-1970 and 1984, 2 folders (Box 97)
      - Rules, 1971-1982 (Box 97)
      - 1964-1965, 2 folders (Box 97)
      - 1968
        - Correspondence (Box 97)
        - Nominee Documentation (Box 97)
        - Press Releases (Box 97)
      - 1969
        - Correspondence (Box 98)
        - Nominee Documentation (Box 98)
      - 1970
        - Correspondence (Box 98)
        - Nominee Documentation (Box 98)
      - 1971-1987, 24 folders (Box 98)
      - 1988-1997, 11 folders (Box 99)
    - Best Chapter Electronic Publication Award, 1998-1999 (Box 99)
    - Chapter Event of the Year Award, 1991 1995-1999, 5 folders (Box 99)
    - Chapter Member of the Year Award, 1991 1995-1999, 7 folders (Box 100)
    - Chapter of the Year Award
      - General, 1982-1997, 29 folders (Box 100)
      - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 101)
      - Nominee Documentation 1998-2000, 13 folders (Box 101)
    - Chapter/SIG Best Publication Award
      (same as Chapter Publication of the Year?)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 101)
      - Criteria, 1972 (Box 101)
      - Samples, 1970 and 1972-1973 (Box 101)
      - General, 1990-1991 1994-1995 1996-1997 1998-1999, 4 folders (Box 101)
    - Dissertation Scholarship, 1979-1982 (Box 101)
    - Distinguished Lecturer Award, 1981 (Box 101)
    - Distinguished Service Award, 1968 (Box 101)
    - Doctoral Forum Award
      - 1974-1989, 7 folders (Box 101)
      - 1990-1996, 9 folders (Box 102)
    - Humphrey Award, 1978-1981 (Box 103)
    - Information Science Book Award
      - Correspondence, 1969-1991 1995-1999, 11 folders (Box 103)
      - Guidelines, 1978-1979 (Box 103)
      - Miscellanea, 1975-1980 (Box 103)
      - Publicity, 1977-1980 (Box 103)
    - ISI Doctoral Dissertation Award
      - 1983-1991, 12 folders (Box 103)
      - 1995-1999, 4 folders (Box 104)
    - ISI Doctoral Dissertation Proposal Scholarship Award, 2000 (Box 104)
    - ISI/ASIS Citation Analysis Research Award, 1999 (Box 104)
    - James B. Cretsos Leadership Award, 1996-1999, 3 folders (Box 104)
    - JASIS Paper Award
      - Correspondence, 1969-1984 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 104)
      - Miscellanea, 1979-1984 (Box 104)
    - Kaskela Award for the Best Newsletter, 1972-1976 (Box 104)
    - Luhn (H. P) Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1965-1967 (Box 104)
    - Non-Print Media Award, 1969-1981 (Box 104)
    - Outstanding Information Science Teacher Award
      - 1979 (Box 104)
      - 1980
        - Correspondence (Box 104)
        - Nominees (Box 104)
        - Press Releases and Tear Sheets (Box 104)
      - 1981
        - Correspondence (Box 104)
        - Guidelines (Box 104)
        - Nominees (Box 104)
      - 1982
        - Correspondence (Box 104)
          (includes Guidelines and Press Releases)
        - Nominees, 2 folders (Box 104)
      - 1983-2000, 20 folders (Box 105)
        (includes correspondence and nominee submissions)
    - Pratt-Severn Best Student Research Paper Award, 1996-1997 1999, 3 folders (Box 106)
      (was Student Paper Contest?)
    - Research Award, 1985 1990 1995-1998, 2 folders (Box 106)
    - SIG of the Year Award
      - 1983-1988 1989, 8 folders (Box 106)
      - 1991-1999, 11 folders (Box 107)
    - SIG Member of the Year Award, 1992-1996 1999, 6 folders (Box 108)
    - SIG Publication of the Year Award, 1992-1997, 5 folders (Box 108)
    - Student Chapter of the Year Award, 1988-1991 1994-1999, 8 folders (Box 108)
    - Student Paper Contest, 1972-1983 1985-1991 1995, 21 folders (Box 109)
    - UMI Doctoral Dissertation Award
      - 1997 1999, 10 folders (Box 110)
      - 2000-2001, 25 folders (Box 111)
    - Watson Davis Award, 1976-1986 1988-1989 1992 1994 1996-1997, 16 folders (Box 112)
- MEMBERSHIP
  The MEMBERSHIP series (2 linear feet) contains materials relating to membership services and promotional materials. It also includes membership lists, reports, and surveys. (There are also some materials on the Operations Planning Task Force. The researcher should consult the Committees series for further material relating to this committee. MEMALERT was an attempt by the Southern Ohio Chapter of ASIS to make membership in ASIS more personal. All new memberships were sent to them, after which they would notify the other local chapters as to who the new members were, so those chapters could contact them. This idea was developed when national headquarters could no longer cope with the flood of new memberships.
  - Advertising, 1992-1993 (Box 113)
  - Alternative Memberships, 1975-1976 (Box 113)
  - Associated Organizations Membership Lists, 1965-1966 (Box 113)
  - Benefits, 1985-1986 (Box 113)
  - Biographies, 1984-1988 (Box 113)
  - Brochures, 1966 1970 1973 (Box 113)
  - Correspondence, 1956-1982 1985-1989 and undated, 7 folders (Box 113)
  - Donors, 1988-1989 (Box 113)
  - Exit Interviews, undated (Box 113)
  - Financial Information, 1991-1992 (Box 113)
  - Hardship/Refunds, 1985-1987 (Box 113)
  - Individuals, 1952 1961 and 1978 (Box 113)
  - Inquiries, general, 1985-1986 (Box 113)
  - Institutional Membership
    - Benefits, 1968-1978 (Box 113)
    - Brochures, 1969-1979 (Box 113)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1991 (Box 113)
    - Financial Information, 1971-1977 (Box 113)
    - Lists, 1960-1977 (Box 113)
    - Procedures, 1979 and undated (Box 113)
  - International Membership, 1985-1988 (Box 113)
  - Internship: Minority Leaders Fellowship Program, 1988 (Box 113)
  - Lapsed Members, 1971-1977 (Box 113)
  - Manual: "A Collection of Ideas about ASIS Membership Promotion," 1979 (Box 113)
  - MEMALERT, 1971-1978 (Box 113)
  - Member Insurance, undated (Box 113)
  - Member Loan Program
    - Correspondence, 1968-1981 1985 (Box 113)
    - Reports, 1977-1981 (Box 113)
  - Membership Campaign, 1971-1980, 2 folders (Box 113)
  - Membership Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 113)
  - Membership Directory, 1969 (Box 113)
  - Membership Finders List, 1975 (Box 113)
  - Membership Lists, 1940 1949 1951-1952 and 1960-1965 (Box 113)
  - Membership Profile, 1980 (Box 113)
  - Membership Promotion, 1964 and 1968 (Box 113)
  - Membership Record Automation, 1970-1974 (Box 113)
  - Membership Record Procedures, 1980-1981 (Box 113)
  - Membership Renewal, 1992 (Box 113)
  - Membership Statistics, undated, 1954 and 1968 (Box 113)
  - Membership Survey Results, 1971 1980, 2 folders (Box 113)
  - Miscellanea, 1967-1974 (Box 113)
  - New Member Kit, undated (Box 113)
  - Operations Planning Task Force, 1978 (Box 113)
    (includes survey of membership services and activities)
  - Paper: "How I Sell the Idea of Information Science as a Profession," 1977 (Box 113)
  - Procedure for 2nd Mailing to Inquiries, 1993 (Box 113)
  - Questionnaires
    - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 113)
    - Membership Profile, 1974-1975 1987 (Box 113)
    - Planning, 1987, 2 folders (Box 114)
  - Reports, 1963-1980 1991-1996 1998-1999, 7 folders (Box 114)
  - Student Membership, 1972-1982 (Box 114)
- PUBLICATIONS
  The PUBLICATIONS series (15 linear feet) contains materials pertaining to the various journals and monographs published by ASIS. General material is followed by materials of and about individual publications, arranged alphabetically by title. All printed materials (except for some newsletters) have been separated from the records. The journals and other publications can be found in the University Library holdings. Some manuscript papers, submitted to BASIS and JASIS, are included under the volume in which they were printed. Publications Committee minutes are located in the Committees series.
  - General
    - Advertising
      - ASIS Ads in Other Publications, 1980 and undated (Box 115)
      - Publication Marketing: Samples, 1986-1987 and undated (Box 115)
      - 50th Anniversary, 1987 (Box 115)
    - ASIS logo, undated (Box 115)
    - Author Contracts, 1974-1981 (Box 115)
    - Auxiliary Publications, 1941-1967 and undated (Box 115)
    - Book Reviewers
      - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 115)
      - Journal Lists, undated, 1974 and 1976 (Box 115)
    - Book Reviews and Announcements, 1975-1977, 3 folders (Box 115)
    - Catalog of Publications, 1972-1973 (Box 115)
    - Cataloging in Publication, 1972-1975 (Box 115)
    - Complimentary Copies, 1975-1976 (Box 115)
    - Contracts
      - Herlitz, 1964 (Box 115)
      - Kraus Reprint Corporation, 1964-1977 (Box 115)
      - Microfiche Systems Corporation, 1972-1974 (Box 115)
      - University Microfilms, 1961-1972 (Box 115)
    - Copyright, 1972-1973 (Box 115)
    - Copyright Releases, 1969-1982, 5 folders (Box 115)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1982, 5 folders (Box 115)
    - Editorial Board
      - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 115)
      - Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 115)
    - Editorial Review, 1978-1979 (Box 115)
    - Financial Information
      - Budgets, 1971-1975 (Box 115)
      - Publication Sales, 1973-1976 (Box 115)
      - Receipts and Disbursements, 1971-1974 (Box 115)
      - Statement of Income, 1973-1974 (Box 115)
    - History, ca. 1975 (Box 115)
    - Job Descriptions, 1974-1976 (Box 115)
    - Knowledge Industry Publications, Inc. (KIPI)
      - Agreement, 1977-1981 and 1985 (Box 115)
      - Catalogs, 1979-1982 (Box 115)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1982 (Box 115)
    - Monograph/Series Editor Search, 1980-1982 (Box 115)
    - Monographs, 1975-1980 (Box 115)
    - News Releases, 1974-1976 (Box 116)
    - Pergamon-Maxwell, 1972-1973 (Box 116)
    - Pergamon Negotiations, 1977 (Box 116)
    - Policy Guidelines, 1971-1982 (Box 116)
    - Port City Press, 1972-1976 (Box 116)
    - Procedures
      - General, 1971-1973 (Box 116)
      - Reduction, 1970-1973 (Box 116)
    - Program Status Report, undated (Box 116)
    - Proposed Publications
      - Correspondence, 1972-1980 (Box 116)
      - Proposals, 1972-1980 (Box 116)
    - Publications Agreement, undated (Box 116)
    - Publications Committee Minutes, 1969-1975, 3 folders (Box 116)
    - Publications Lists, 1965-1981 (Box 116)
    - Publications Schedules, 1975-1977 (Box 116)
    - Publicity, 1979 (Box 116)
    - Publishers' Bids, 1975-1976 (Box 116)
    - Report to the ASIS Publications Committee on the ADI/ASIS Publications (Serials) Program, 1982 (Box 116)
    - Reprint Policy, 1970-1972 (Box 116)
    - Reprints Permission, 1970-1976, 2 folders (Box 116)
    - Royalty Payments, 1969 (Box 116)
    - Sales Reports, 1966-1977, 3 folders (Box 116)
    - Surveys: Readership/Publications Surveys, 1987 (Box 116)
    - Technical Program Activities, 1976 (Box 116)
    - "Topics" Reference Files, 1982-1987 (Box 116)
    - UNESCO Editors Symposium, 1972 (Box 116)
    - Yellow Pages Ideas, 1988-1990 (Box 116)
  - Individual Publications
    - ARIST ( Annual Review of Information Science and Technology)
      - Advisor Roster, 1966-1971 (Box 116)
      - Advisors, 1966-1972 (Box 116)
      - Advisory Board Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 116)
      - Authors and Typist's Guide, 1971 (Box 116)
      - Bibliographic Support, 1968-1972
        - General Information, December 1971-January 1972 (Box 116)
        - Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 116)
        - Final Report, 1970 (Box 116)
        - Journal Coverage, 1968-1972 (Box 116)
        - Journals Dropped, 1971 (Box 116)
        - Proposal, 1969-1970 (Box 116)
        - Users' Reactions, 1969 (Box 116)
      - Bibliographic Support, 1972-1975
        - General Information, 1972-1975 (Box 116)
        - Journals Selected, 1973 (Box 116)
        - Statistics, 1975 (Box 117)
      - Bibliography, 1968-1975, 2 folders (Box 117)
      - Brochures, 1966-1972 (Box 117)
      - Chapter Reprint Series, 1976 (Box 117)
      - Chapter, Titles and Author Addresses, Vol. 1-20, 1985 (Box 117)
      - Contracts: with North and Battelle, 1970 (Box 117)
      - Conversion Chart, undated (Box 117)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1975, 15 folders (Box 117)
      - Cost Data, 1971-1972 (Box 117)
      - Cumulative Index, 1975 (Box 117)
        (includes correspondence with Jessica Harris)
      - Editor Selection Committee, 1974, 2 folders (Box 117)
      - Editorial Policy, 1979 (Box 117)
      - Editorial Process, 1968-1972 (Box 117)
      - Encyclopedia Britannica
        - Agreement, 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 117)
        - Correspondence, 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 117)
      - Final Reports: "Impact Study of the Annual Review of Information Science and Technology," 1968 (Box 118)
      - Foreign Language Coverage, 1971 (Box 118)
      - "Guide for the Preparation of Bibliographic References," 1975 (Box 118)
      - HEW Grant Information, 1968-1971 (Box 118)
      - Index, 1972-1976 (Box 118)
      - Journals, 1970-1971 (Box 118)
      - Manpower Requirements, 1973 (Box 118)
      - Manuscript Outlines, 1969-1975 and undated (Box 118)
      - Merged Listing, 1970 and 1974 (Box 118)
      - National Science Foundation Grant, 1964-1967 (Box 118)
      - Progress Reports, 1965-1970, 2 folders (Box 118)
      - Proposals
        - National Library of Medicine, 1973-1974 (Box 118)
        - From ADI to NSF, undated (Box 118)
        - To Publishers (non-NSF), 1964-1965 (Box 118)
      - Publishers, 1965-1967 (Box 118)
      - Reviews and Evaluations, 1967-1974, 2 folders (Box 118)
      - Speeches, 1971 and undated (Box 118)
      - System Development Corporation
        - Correspondence, 1965-1972, 3 folders (Box 118)
        - Proposal: from Carlos Cuadra, 1972-1973 (Box 118)
      - Vol. 1-11: Table of Contents, 1966-1976c (Box 118)
      - Volume 6: Bibliographic Support, 1969-1971, 2 folders (Box 118)
      - Volume 7
        - Bibliographic Support, 1969-1971 (Box 118)
        - Chapter
          - Introduction, 1972 (Box 118)
          - Outlines, 1972 (Box 118)
          - Summaries, 1972 (Box 118)
        - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 118)
      - Volume 8
        - Author Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 118)
        - Authors, undated (Box 118)
        - Chapter Summaries, 1973 (Box 118)
      - Volume 9
        - Author Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 118)
        - Authors, 1973-1974 (Box 118)
        - Bibliographic Support, May-September 1973, 4 folders (Box 118)
        - Chapter Outlines, 1973 (Box 118)
      - Volume 10
        - Authors, undated (Box 118)
        - Bibliographic Support, 1974 (Box 119)
          - Outline, 1975 and undated (Box 119)
          - July 1974-January 1975, 6 folders (Box 119)
        - Chapter Outlines, 1975 (Box 119)
        - Complimentary Book List, undated (Box 119)
        - Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 119)
      - Volume 11
        - Bibliographic Support, October -November 1975 (Box 119)
        - Chapters, 1976 (Box 119)
        - Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 119)
        - Task and Manpower Requirements, undated (Box 119)
      - Volume 12
        - Authors, 1976 (Box 119)
        - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 119)
      - Volume 13
        - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 119)
    - American Documentation
      - Copyright, 1968-1969 (Box 119)
      - Correspondence
        - Gull, C.D.: re Jesse Shera contract, 1960 (Box 119)
        - General, 1961 (Box 119)
      - Royalty Payments, 1968-1974 (Box 119)
      - Subscriptions: Watson Davis, 1951 (Box 119)
    - Annual Meeting
      (draft or proof copies)
      - Collected Papers and Abstracts, 1986 (Box 119)
      - Final Program, 1987-1988 (Box 119)
    - Archival Automation Symposium Proceedings Correspondence, 1982 (Box 119)
    - The Auerbach Annual Best Computer Papers, 1979-1981 (Box 119)
    - BASIS ( Bulletin of the American Society for Information Science)
      - Advertising
        - General, 1974-1980 1983-1984, 2 folders (Box 119)
        - Ad Prospects, 1987 and undated (Box 119)
        - Advertisements, 1983-1985, 3 folders (Box 119)
        - Extra Forms, undated (Box 119)
        - Monthly advertiser lists
          - February 1987-1991 (Box 119)
          - April 1990-1991 (Box 119)
          - August 1986-1990 (Box 119)
          - October 1986-1990 (Box 119)
          - December 1986-1990 (Box 119)
        - Rates, 1988 (Box 119)
      - Advisory Board
        - Correspondence, 1974-1979 (Box 119)
        - Members, 1974-1977 (Box 119)
        - Minutes, 1979 (Box 119)
      - Biographies, undated (Box 119)
      - Columnists, 1974-1980 (Box 120)
      - Complimentary Copies, 1974-1980 (Box 120)
      - Contributing Editors
        - General, 1974-1979 (Box 120)
        - Abbott, George, 1978-1981 (Box 120)
        - Aines, Andrew, 1975-1980 (Box 120)
        - Albert, Theodore, 1975 (Box 120)
        - Atchison, William, 1975 (Box 120)
        - Auerbach, Isaac, 1975 (Box 120)
        - Berninger, Doug, 1978 (Box 120)
        - Bracken, Marilyn, 1974-1975 (Box 120)
        - Brandhorst, W. Theodore, 1974-1976 (Box 120)
        - Brong, Gerald, 1975-1980 (Box 120)
        - Burchinal, Lee, 1974-1976 (Box 120)
        - Butler, Brett, 1975-1979 (Box 120)
        - Caponio, Joseph F, 1978 (Box 120)
        - Chartrand, Robert L., 1974-1975 (Box 120)
        - Clemens, Thomas, 1975 (Box 120)
        - Cotton, Ira, 1975-1978 (Box 120)
        - Day, Melvin, 1975-1976 (Box 120)
        - Deahl, Thomas, 1974 (Box 120)
        - Debons, Anthony, 1975 (Box 120)
        - Edward, Charles, 1977-1978 (Box 120)
        - Engle, Ralph L., Jr., 1974-1979 (Box 120)
        - Henderson, Madeline, 1982 (Box 120)
        - Herner, Saul, 1979 (Box 120)
        - Herrmann, Roy, 1975 (Box 120)
        - Hlava, Marjorie M. K., 1979 (Box 120)
        - Hoshovsky, Alexander G., 1975 (Box 120)
        - Kadec, Sarah Thomas, 1978 (Box 120)
        - Katz, Ruth, 1975 (Box 120)
        - Kenney, Brigitte L., 1975 (Box 120)
        - Kuney, Joseph H., 1975-1977 (Box 120)
        - Lancaster, F. Wilfred, 1979 (Box 120)
        - Meadows, Charles T., 1975 (Box 120)
        - Mersley, Roy, 1978-1979 (Box 120)
        - Richardson, John, 1975-1976 (Box 120)
        - Sessions, Vivian, 1975-1976 (Box 120)
        - Summit, Roger, 1974-1976 (Box 120)
        - Taylor, Robert S., 1975 (Box 120)
        - Werdel, Judith A., 1974-1980 (Box 120)
        - Williams, Martha, 1975-1976 (Box 120)
      - Copyright, 1974-1982 (Box 120)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1982, 5 folders (Box 120)
      - Correspondence, of Lois Lunin, 1974-1980 (Box 120)
      - Early History, 1973-1974 (Box 120)
        (includes correspondence dealing with publication of BASIS)
      - Editor Search: correspondence dealing with, 1980 (Box 120)
      - Editor Search: correspondence with Anne Armstrong and Edith Holmes, 1980 (Box 120)
      - Editorial Board, 1973-1979 (Box 120)
        (includes minutes)
      - Evaluation Survey, 1980 (Box 120)
      - Evaluation Survey Report, 1980 (Box 120)
      - Fact Sheets, 1975-1980 (Box 121)
      - Federal Information Update: Sources, 1988-1989 (Box 121)
      - Historical, 1987-1988 (Box 121)
      - Incites, 1974-1975 (Box 121)
      - Index, 1975-1976 (Box 121)
      - Info News, 1975 (Box 121)
      - Information Reader Card, 1978 (Box 121)
      - Infy/Ffrogs, 1974 and undated 1979 (Box 121)
        (cartoon sketches intended to be used as information science-related teaching aids and publicity)
      - Inside ASIS, 1987 (Box 121)
      - Internship, 1978 (Box 121)
      - Layout and Format, 1975-1976 (Box 121)
      - Letters to the Editor: A-Z, 1974-1981, 4 folders (Box 121)
      - Media Info, 1988 and undated (Box 121)
      - News, 1974-1978 (Box 121)
      - Newsletter for Editors, 1974-1979 (Box 121)
      - Placement, 1974 (Box 121)
      - Printing, 1983-1988 (Box 121)
      - Procedures, 1974-1980 (Box 121)
      - Production Schedule, 1975-1980 (Box 121)
      - Progress Reports, 1975-1980 (Box 121)
      - Promotion and Advertising, 1974-1980 (Box 122)
      - Proposals, 1973 (Box 122)
      - Publications by Lois Lunin, undated, 1971 and 1974 (Box 122)
      - Remittances, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 122)
      - Reviews, 1974 (Box 122)
      - Style Guide, 1974-1980 (Box 122)
      - Survey Questionnaire
        - Questionnaires, 1973 1980, 2 folders (Box 122)
        - Analysis, 1973 (Box 122)
      - Trademark, 1973-1974 (Box 122)
      - Miscellanea, 1979-1981 (Box 122)
      - Individual Issue Manuscripts
        (includes some correspondence)
        - Volume 1
          - no. 1, June -July 1974 (Box 122)
          - no. 2, August -September 1974 (Box 122)
          - no. 3, October 1974 (Box 122)
          - no. 4, November 1974 (Box 122)
          - no. 5, December 1974 (Box 122)
          - no. 6, January 1975 (Box 122)
          - no. 7, February 1975 (Box 122)
          - no. 8, March 1975 (Box 122)
          - no. 9, April 1975 (Box 122)
          - no. 10, May 1975 (Box 122)
        - Volume 2
          - no. 1, June -July 1975, 4 folders (Box 123)
          - no. 3, September -October 1975, 2 folders (Box 123)
          - no. 4, November 1975 (Box 123)
          - no. 5, December 1975 (Box 123)
          - no. 6, January 1976 (Box 123)
          - no. 7, February 1976 (Box 123)
          - no. 8, March 1976 (Box 123)
          - no. 9, April 1976, 3 folders (Box 123)
            (never published, includes mock-up)
          - no. 10, May 1976 (Box 123)
            (never published, includes mock-up and index to volume 2)
        - Volume 3
          - no. 1, October 1976 (Box 123)
          - no. 2, December 1976, 3 folders (Box 123)
          - no. 3, February 1977 (Box 124)
          - no. 4, April 1977 (Box 124)
          - no. 5, June. 1977 (Box 124)
          - no. 6, August 1977 (Box 124)
        - Volume 4
          - no. 1, October 1977 (Box 124)
          - no. 2, December 1977 (Box 124)
          - no. 3, February 1978 (Box 124)
          - no. 4, April 1978 (Box 124)
          - no. 5, June 1978 (Box 124)
          - no. 6, August 1978 (Box 124)
        - Volume 5
          - no. 1, October 1978 (Box 124)
          - no. 2, December 1978 (Box 124)
          - no. 3, February 1979 (Box 124)
          - no. 4, April 1979 (Box 124)
          - no. 5, June 1979 (Box 124)
          - no. 6, August 1979 (Box 124)
        - Volume 6
          - no. 1, October 1979 (Box 125)
          - no. 2, December 1979 (Box 125)
    - BLIS ( Bibliography on Library and Information Science), 1976 (Box 125)
    - Bibliographic Control for the Information Sciences, 1967-1969 (Box 125)
    - Cable Libraries Newsletter, 1972-1974, 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Computer Science Resources: A Guide to Professional Literature, 1980-1982 (Box 125)
    - Computer-Readable Bibliographic Data Bases: A Directory and Data Sourcebook, 1976-1982 (Box 125)
    - Consultants Directory, 1971-1972 (Box 125)
    - Continuing Library and Information Science Education: A Final Report to the National Commission on Libraries and Information Science, 1970-1974 (Box 125)
    - Copyright Study Group, 1973 (Box 125)
    - Cost Reduction for Special Libraries and Information Centers, 1972-1974 (Box 125)
    - Curricula in Information Science, 1968-1971 (Box 125)
    - Directory of Education for Information Science
      - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1971-1972 (Box 125)
      - Manuscript, 1971-1972 (Box 125)
    - Directory of Information Science Schools
      - Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 125)
      - Meeting Notes, 1971-1973 (Box 125)
      - Miscellanea, 1971-1973 includes Proposal for Long Range ASIS Project in Education for Information Science (Box 125)
    - Documentation Abstracts, 1966 (Box 125)
    - ERIC Clearinghouse, 1975-1976 (Box 125)
    - Energy Information Resources, 1974 (Box 125)
    - FID Publications: to be distributed in U.S. and Canada, 1975-1976 (Box 125)